(singers vocalizing)
♪ Rockin' around
the Christmas tree ♪
♪ At the Christmas party hop ♪
♪ Mistletoe hung
where you can see ♪
♪ Every couple tries to stop ♪
♪ Rockin' around
the Christmas tree ♪
♪ Let the Christmas
spirit ring ♪
♪ Later we'll have
some pumpkin pie ♪
♪ And we'll do some caroling ♪
♪ You will get a
sentimental feeling ♪
♪ When you hear ♪
♪ Voices singing,
let's be jolly ♪
♪ Deck the halls with
boughs of holly ♪
♪ Rockin' around
the Christmas tree ♪
♪ Have a happy holiday ♪
♪ Everyone dancin' merrily ♪
♪ In the new old-fashioned way ♪
(upbeat saxophone music)
(singers vocalizing)
♪ You will get a
sentimental feeling ♪
♪ When you hear ♪
♪ Voices singing,
let's be jolly ♪
♪ Deck the halls with
boughs of holly ♪
♪ Rockin' around
the Christmas tree ♪
♪ Have a happy holiday ♪
♪ Everyone dancin' merrily ♪
♪ In the new old-fashioned way ♪
(singers vocalizing)
(upbeat saxophone music)